[
    {
        "option1": "There is no good man in this village.",
        "option2": "Not a good man has in this village.",
        "option3": "Not good man is there in this village.",
        "option4": "There is not good man in this village.",
        "question": "এই গ্রামে কোনো ভালো মানুষ নেই",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "In this village there is not even a good man.",
        "option2": "There is not even one good man in this village.",
        "option3": "Even one good man has not in this village.",
        "option4": "There is no even one good man in this village.",
        "question": "এই গ্রামে একটাও ভালো মানুষ নেই",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I told to you, I told a story to you.",
        "option2": "I told you, I told to you a story.",
        "option3": "I told you, I told a story to you.",
        "option4": "I told to you, I told a story you.",
        "question": "আমি তোমায় বলেছিলাম, আমি তোমায় গল্প বলেছিলাম",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I have given to you, I have given letter to you.",
        "option2": "I have given you, I have given letter to you.",
        "option3": "I have given you, I have given to you letter.",
        "option4": "I have given to you, I have given letter you.",
        "question": "আমি তোমায় দিয়েছি, আমি তোমায় চিঠি দিয়েছি",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Abheda teaches English, Abheda teaches to us English.",
        "option2": "Abheda teaches in English, Abheda teaches in English to us.",
        "option3": "Abheda teaches in English, Abheda teaches English to us.",
        "option4": "Abheda teaches English, Abheda teaches us English.",
        "question": "অভেদ ইংরাজি শেখায়, অভেদ আমাদের ইংরাজি শেখায়",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "The teacher will ask a question, the teacher will ask me a question.",
        "option2": "The teacher will ask a question, the teacher will ask to me a question.",
        "option3": "The teacher will ask for a question, the teacher will ask a question to me.",
        "option4": "The teacher will ask for a question, the teacher will ask a question me.",
        "question": "শিক্ষক একটা প্রশ্ন জিগ্যেস করবেন, শিক্ষক আমায় একটা প্রশ্ন জিগ্যেস করবেন",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I met wth him and spoke with him.",
        "option2": "I met him and spoke to him.",
        "option3": "I met him and spoke with him.",
        "option4": "I met with him and spoke to him.",
        "question": "আমি তার সঙ্গে দেখা করলাম এবং তার সঙ্গে কথা বললাম",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I taught.",
        "option2": "I did teaching.",
        "option3": "I used to teach.",
        "option4": "I was teaching.",
        "question": "আমি শিক্ষকতা করতাম",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I played cricket, now I am about to play again.",
        "option2": "I used to play cricket, now I am about play again.",
        "option3": "I used to play cricket, now I am about to play again.",
        "option4": "I played cricket, now I am about play again.",
        "question": "আমি আগে ক্রিকেট খেলতাম, এখন আবার এই খেলতে যাচ্ছি",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Would you like a drink ?",
        "option2": "Would you like to a drink ?",
        "option3": "Will you want a drink ?",
        "option4": "Will you take a drink ?",
        "question": "আপনি কি একটি পানীয় নেবেন (পছন্দ করবেন) ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Yes, I shall take coffee, please give me a cup of coffee.",
        "option2": "Yes, I would like coffee, give me a cup of coffee.",
        "option3": "Yes, I would like coffee, please give me a cup of coffee.",
        "option4": "Yes, I want coffee, please give me a cup of coffee.",
        "question": "হ্যাঁ, আমি কফি নেব, আমায় দয়া করে এক কাপ কফি দিন",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "You read all examples again, tell them to me.",
        "option2": "You please read to all examples again, please tell them to me.",
        "option3": "Read all examples again, please tell them to me.",
        "option4": "Read to all examples again, please tell them to me.",
        "question": "সবকটা উদাহরণ আবার পড়ো, দয়া করে আমায় ওগুলো বলো",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "You have completed 500 examples, thank to you.",
        "option2": "You completed 500 examples, thank you.",
        "option3": "You completed 500 examples, thank to you.",
        "option4": "You have completed 500 examples, thank you.",
        "question": "তুমি/তোমরা ৫০০ উদাহরণ শেষ করেছো, ধন্যবাদ",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]